fahadmehmood669@gmail.com | 03132677203 | Karachi, Sindh 12311



# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced Depot Incharge and Data Entry Officer with over 5 years of experience in the Industry. With a get it done approach and excellent problem solving skill, I always achieve my goals no matter the task. And always motivated to learn, and get better in Industry.

#### **SKILLS**

- Operating System (Windows XP Professional, Windows Vista and Windows 7).
- Ms Word
- · Ms Excel

- Typing Speed 20 wpm English.
- · S&D Pro

#### WORKING EXPERIENCE

Jan 2018 - Sep 2019

### **Depot Incharge**

- · Evaluated products to determine quality levels and discard faulty products.
- Juice Pack Industries Karachi, Sindh Transported Products to customer locations.
  - Handled calls to address customer inquiries and concerns.

Sep 2015 - Nov 2017

### **Sales Officer**

Engro Eximp Agriproducts - Karachi, Sindh

- Managed a business of 1.5 Million PKR and achieved monthly targets successfully.
- Accomplished a growth of 12% on monthly basis in the territory of Malir Town.
- Developed routing of the area with supervisor in order to optimize sales.
- Maintained shelves & counter Displays at retail stores
- · Maintained company's KPIs like Productivity, Call Productivity, SKU per bill and drop size of stores.
- · Actively worked with merchandising teams to support them and to visible products for improved off takes.
- Maintained good relationships through effective communication with trade.
- 2 years experience at System Limited as a Data Entry Officer.

#### **EDUCATION**

### **High School Diploma**

St. Gabriel School

Have Passed Matriculation Examination in Science Group from the Board of Karachi.

#### **Technical Qualification**

Aman Tech

Completed 1 year Mechanical Diploma from Aman Tech Foundation, Karachi in 2014

fahadmehmood669@gmail.com | 03132677203 | Karachi, Sindh 12311



# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced Depot Incharge and Data Entry Officer with over 5 years of experience in the Industry. With a get it done approach and excellent problem solving skill, I always achieve my goals no matter the task. And always motivated to learn, and get better in Industry.

### **SKILLS**

- Operating System (Windows XP Professional, Windows Vista and Windows 7).
- Ms Word
- · Ms Excel

- Typing Speed 20 wpm English.
- · S&D Pro

#### WORKING EXPERIENCE

Jan 2018 - Sep 2019

### **Depot Incharge**

- · Evaluated products to determine quality levels and discard faulty products.
- Juice Pack Industries Karachi, Sindh Transported Products to customer locations.
  - Handled calls to address customer inquiries and concerns.

Sep 2015 - Nov 2017

### **Sales Officer**

Engro Eximp Agriproducts - Karachi, Sindh

- Managed a business of 1.5 Million PKR and achieved monthly targets successfully.
- Accomplished a growth of 12% on monthly basis in the territory of Malir Town.
- Developed routing of the area with supervisor in order to optimize sales.
- Maintained shelves & counter Displays at retail stores
- · Maintained company's KPIs like Productivity, Call Productivity, SKU per bill and drop size of stores.
- · Actively worked with merchandising teams to support them and to visible products for improved off takes.
- Maintained good relationships through effective communication with trade.
- 2 years experience at System Limited as a Data Entry Officer.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **High School Diploma**

St. Gabriel School

Have Passed Matriculation Examination in Science Group from the Board of Karachi.

#### **Technical Qualification**

Aman Tech

Completed 1 year Mechanical Diploma from Aman Tech Foundation, Karachi in 2014